Sanni Habib

Fullstack web developer

6, Adedoyin street, Epe, Lagos, Nigeria sannihabib001@gmail.com

I am a student with vast interest in creating well functional and exquisite projects and web solutions with a company of similar goals. I'm hoping to work for at least five hours per day.

Over three years of professional experience has led to my proficiency in fullstack web development. I have also completed a series of projects including e-commerce sites, blogs, mobile app, desktop app and more over this period of time.

SKILLS

FRONTEND

- HTML, CSS
- Javascript
- JQuery
- Styled-components
- React
- Typescript
- Redux

BACKEND

- PHP (Laravel)
- Java (Springboot)
- Nodejs

OTHER TECHNOLOGIES

- MySQL
- PgSQL
- MongoDB/Mongoose
- Docker
- Git/Github actions

EXPERIENCE

Harnix-Tech, Remote - Fullstack developer

SEPTEMBER 2019 - NOVEMBER 2020

- Majorly contributed on the backend role
- Reviewed frontend codes and web UI
- Database integration and maintenance
- Security checks and management

Genius Codes (Team), Lagos - Fullstack developer

FEBRUARY 2021 - JANUARY 2022

- Developed several functional websites
- Adopted different technologies for backend service
- Worked as a team and lead numbers of projects
- Created a lot of APIs with efficient algorithms

EDUCATION

Obafemi Awolowo University, Osun- *Bsc. Electrical and Electronics Engineering*

2019 - PRESENT

I had a breakthrough into this university, as I gained my admission on merit. It's been really great all through with my academics. I'm also glad to have learnt a lot with both hardware and software, and also gaining more ground with developing efficient algorithms. I hope to make spectacular projects with my hardware and software skills in future, still chasing my dreams.

AWARDS

2nd Place (in Country) - IEEExtreme Worldwide hackathon, 2021.

Winner - Bayview Hackathon, 2022.

STEM Ambassador - IEEE OAU